https://bugcentral.com/privacy-policy-2/

Privacy Policy
This is the privacy policy that applies to this Site and our services. We have a firm commitment to safeguarding the privacy of our customers’ personal information. Personal information is information about an identifiable individual. Publicly available information, such as a public directory listing of your name, address, telephone number, or electronic address, is not considered to be personal information.COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONWhen you make a payment on our website we ask for information such as your name, organization name, and email address. We also collect the e-mail addresses and other personal information provided during email inquiries. Information we collect is stored on computer servers that we use to operate the Site except credit card information.The personal information we collect is used to provide our products and services, for billing, for identification and authentication, for the general operation and improvement of our service, and to respond to inquiries, and is not used, shared with or sold to other organizations, except: to our service providers, as required to operate the Site and provide the products or services you’ve requested; to the applicable customer of the account in respect of which contact information is submitted to us; for collection purposes; to law enforcement agencies, in emergencies, for internal security matters, or where required by court order or search warrant; or when we have your permission.We may also disclose personal information in connection with the transfer to the acquirer upon the sale of our business.We may also record your computer’s IP address with your order to help us identify fraudulent credit card use. We may share this information with the financial institution that issued the credit card with which an order was placed or with law enforcement authorities if we determine, or are notified, that the use of the credit card was fraudulent.Your personal information is not used or disclosed by us for any other purpose.COOKIESA cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are required to use our service. We use cookies to record user session information.SECURITYThe security of your personal information is important to us. Our service has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We do not store credit card information in our database. We follow generally accepted industry practices to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Site, you can email us at the address below.CHANGESBy using this Site, you agree that you permit the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. From time to time, we may make changes to our Privacy Policy and you should review it periodically for any changes. Your continued use of this Site following the effective date of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes, subject to your continuing right to notify us at any time as to how you would like us to treat your personal information.QUESTIONSYou can contact us with any questions about this Privacy Policy at info@bug-central.com
PO Box 2001Orange, CA 92859info@bug-central.comStructural Pest Control BoardLic. #PR3221We are fully licensed, bonded, and insured.
(562) 774-1111(213) 674-4416(310) 295-2280(323) 476-1118(626) 389-8904(818) 435-7799
